{
    "subject": "resource/Dangerous_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "Dangerous",
    "human_readable": "The title of the film is 'Dangerous'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7176663875579834,
            "question": "Who might have directed the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6902150511741638,
            "question": "When was the film 'Dangerous' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6707368493080139,
            "question": "What is the main theme explored in the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.605612576007843,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'Dangerous' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.547479510307312,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5059176087379456,
            "question": "What is the title of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5047671794891357,
            "question": "Where can I watch the film 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49993014335632324,
            "question": "Has the film 'Dangerous' won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.487021267414093,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about the plot of 'Dangerous'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14676323533058167,
            "question": "Is this a film or something else?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of the film is 'Dangerous'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4094_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me more about the plot of 'Dangerous'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4094_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has the film 'Dangerous' won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4094_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch the film 'Dangerous'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4094_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4094_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention a film titled \"Dangerous,\" which directly supports the query about the title of the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}